Daffa Putera Kouseina, Mobile Developer

Purwokerto, Indonesia, +6281325218571, kouseinadaffa@gmail.com

LINKS	Portfolio, Github, Youtube, Playstore		
PROFILE	I'm a mobile developer. I have 3 years of experience in mobile development. I have built many Android and iOS with flutter framework. By working on those projects, I accrued an imposing skill set, which has taught me punctuality.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Mar 2024 — Present	Mobile Developer, PT. Satu Vis	i Raya (SAVIR)	Purwokerto
	As a Mobile Developer at Satu Visi Raya, I played a key role in developing and maintaining mobile app. My technical expertise in Flutter, enabled me to contribute to the team. I was involved in the full software development lifecycle, from concept to deployment, ensuring high-quality and efficient software solutions.		
Jul 2023 — Jul 2024	Mobile Developer, Dealjava		Medan
	methodology - Define git rules, folders, code, etc.	nt process through the entire software life cycle u ies such as Flutter, Bloc, Stream, Rest Api th and wireless	nder Waterfall
Oct 2021 — May 2023	Mobile Developer, PT. RAKHA	ASA ARTHA WISESA	Jakarta
	methodology - Define git rules, folders, code, etc Handling playstore, appstore, firebase	ies such as Flutter, Getx, Firebase, Git, Rest Api,	
Oct 2020 — Nov 2021	Software Engineer, Freelance (S	elf employed)	Purwokerto
 Create app for helps the growth of premature babies on a regular basis, stores data Health Services for Premature Babies. Create news portal application, which contains about digital coins. Create application for ordering food online and has 2 applications, namely for ore Create application to provide tourist information around Bandung. Create simple Android App, to find out market in Lampung, with Java Create an application for daily prayers in Islam, etc 		contains about digital coins. nline and has 2 applications, namely for ordering nformation around Bandung. ut market in Lampung, with Java	
EDUCATION			
Oct 2023 — Present	Informatics Engineering, STMIK Widya Utama		Purwokerto
SKILLS	Flutter	Git	
	Kotlin	Playstore & Appstore	
	Java	Android & IOS	
HOBBIES	I would like to join tech competition like hackaton or something else. Such as codefest asia, permata youth preneur, invofest, etc.		